Play at your own risk.
The Sonata is a horror, thriller, mystery film directed by Andrew Desmond.
After a gifted musician inherits a mansion after her long lost father dies under mysterious circumstances, she discovers his last musical
masterpiece riddled with cryptic symbols that unravels an evil secret, triggering dark forces that reach beyond her imagination.
Rose Fisher, played by Freya Tingley.
Charles Vernais, played by Simon Abkarian.
Sir Victor Ferdinand, played by James Faulkner.
Richard Marlowe, played by Rutger Hauer.
Thérèse, played by Catherine Schaub-Abkarian.
James, played by Matt Barber.
Autumn Sonata (Swedish: Höstsonaten) is a 1978 tragedy film written and directed by Ingmar Bergman,
and starring Ingrid Bergman (in her final film role), Liv Ullmann and Lena Nyman.
Its plot follows a celebrated classical pianist and her neglected daughter who meet for the first time
in years, and chronicles their painful discussions of how they have hurt each other.
It was the only collaboration between Ingrid Bergman and
Ingmar Bergman (who were not related).
Autumn Sonata was the last of Ingmar Bergman's films to be made for theatrical exhibition; all of his
films made after it, even those screened in theatres, were television productions.
The film explores themes of violin, sonata, creepy house.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.